Everybody remembers it how they need to.
Jersey Boys is a music, drama film directed by Clint Eastwood.
A musical biopic of the Four Seasons—the rise, the tough times and personal clashes, and the
ultimate triumph of a group of friends whose music became symbolic of a generation.
Far from a mere tribute concert, it gets to the heart of the relationships at the centre of the group,
with a special focus on frontman Frankie Valli, the small kid with the big falsetto.
Francis 'Frankie Valli' Castelluccio, played by John Lloyd Young.
Gaetano 'Tommy' DeVito, played by Vincent Piazza.
Nick Massi, played by Michael Lomenda.
Bob Gaudio, played by Erich Bergen.
Angelo 'Gyp' DeCarlo, played by Christopher Walken.
Bob Crewe, played by Mike Doyle.
Jersey Boys is a 2014 American  musical drama film directed and produced by Clint
Eastwood, based on the 2004 Tony Award-winning jukebox musical of the same name.
The film tells the story of the musical group The Four Seasons.
Original band members Frankie Valli and Bob Gaudio (who also
composed the film's music) were executive producers.
Jersey Boys was released in the United States on June 20, 2014.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the musical numbers but
criticized the narrative and runtime, and grossed $67 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of musical, biography, based on play or musical.
The tone is emotional.